Guide to the Brooklyn Arts Council Folk Arts collection CBHM.0002
Center for Brooklyn History
Brooklyn Arts Council Folk Arts collection
1900-2013
1986-2013
Center for Brooklyn History
Brooklyn Arts Council
CBHM.0002
64.8 Linear Feet 4 record cartons, 8 large flat boxes, 9 small flat boxes, 36 media boxes, and 51 manuscript boxes
Materials produced from 1986-2013 by Folk Arts, a program of Brooklyn Arts Council, created to celebrate, document, and educate the public about folk arts traditions in Brooklyn through song and dance performances, craft demonstrations, film screenings, and art exhibits. Program files include event planning materials, promotional items, budget information, research materials, and artist files. The collection includes extensive audiovisual documentation of events, artist submissions, and oral history interviews. Items dated 1900-1985 collected for submissions and research are also included.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Gift of the Brooklyn Arts Council, 2021.
Physical Characteristics and Technical Requirements
The majority of the materials in this collection are stored offsite and advance notice is required for use. Please contact cbhreference@bklynlibrary.org at least two weeks prior to research visit.
All audiovisual materials including cassettes, VHS tapes, mini DV cassettes, mini discs, and AMPEX Grand Master 457 1/4'' reels are unavailable due to technical limitations.
If digital surrogates exist, they should be used in place of the originals whenever possible.
Access
Certain participants in Black Brooklyn Renaissance: Black Arts and Culture 1960-2010 have not granted permission for their likeness to appear in any related media. See box 28, folder 1 for a full list. Due to sensitive personal information, certain materials in boxes 98 and 100 are restricted. Other materials open to researchers without restriction.
Related Materials
Bob Gore photograph collection, BCMS.0049
West Indian Carnival Documentation Project records, 2010.019
Oral Histories:
New Neighbors: Sunset Park's Chinese Community oral histories 1994.007
Puerto Rican Oral History Project 1976.001
Muslims in Brooklyn oral histories 2018.006
Arrangement
This collection is composed of fourteen series, arranged alphabetically by project title except for Early Programs, which appears at the beginning, and Brooklyn Arts Council Materials, which appears at the end. Each series includes Program Files, usually arranged chronologically or by topic and Audiovisual materials, usually arranged by format. Artist files and interviews are arranged alphabetically. Visual materials produced for Local Eyes is interfiled in the Program Files sub-series. September 11th Memorial Projects is arranged chronologically in seven sub-series, with Program Files and Audiovisual items interfiled.
Scope and Contents
This collection is composed of materials produced for Folk Arts, a multi-year grant funded program to celebrate, document, and educate the public about folk arts traditions in Brooklyn. The Early Programs series includes documentation of events produced from 1986-2000. Program Files include event financial information, planning documents, notes from various Folklorists, research materials, and extensive audiovisual documentation. See series level for a full description.
Series 2-13 includes materials for single and multi-year events produced from 2000-2013. Program Files include event planning, press, budget information, research materials, and correspondence. Artist files include releases and biographical information. Cassettes, VHS tapes, discs, minidiscs, photographs and slides make up the audiovisual materials, and include event documentation, artist submissions, and oral history interviews. Photographs are both print and digital. Digital photographs are stored on discs. See series levels for full descriptions.
Brochures and film festival materials produced for Brooklyn Arts Council events not associated with the Folk Arts program are housed in Series 14.
Historical Note
The Brooklyn Arts Council was founded by Charlene Victor in 1966 as the Brooklyn Arts and Cultural Association (BACA). The program worked to facilitate collaborations between Brooklyn's large cultural heritage institutions, such as the Brooklyn Museum and the Brooklyn Academy of Music, with local artists, musicians, and galleries. BACA worked to secure grants for artists and programs with a focus on Brooklyn neighborhoods typically underserved by cultural heritage programming. In 1986 BACA formally changed its name to Brooklyn Arts Council (BAC).
In 1988, BAC received a grant from the New York State Council on the Arts (NYSCA) as part of an effort to place folk arts programs in counties across New York state to do field research, create documentation, produce programming, and provide assistance to other organizations interested in developing programs. In addition to Brooklyn, programs were started in Buffalo, Corning, and Binghamton. NYSCA provided funding and assisted with developing guidelines, hiring, and site visits. BAC employee Kathleen Condon was awarded an additional grant to receive a salary as the program's first Folklorist.
Following BAC's model, Folk Arts prioritized neighborhoods typically overlooked for cultural heritage programming, and communities which often lacked venues to stage events. Condon solved this by developing a relationship with the Brooklyn Public Library to use library branches as performance spaces. Early events included Alvin Forteau and the Caribbean Dancers (Trinidadian dancing and drumming), Lillian Habib (Lebanese cooking), Jamila and Mahmood Masumi and Nafas Gul Muradi (Afghan rug weaving and design), and Doris Jensen (Norwegian rosemaler). Condon oversaw all marketing and outreach, often relying on the host libraries to send out press releases and hiring community members to hand out flyers.
BAC had to reapply every year for the Folklorist salary grant. The position was part time, and after Condon's 1989 departure the position was held by a series of early career professionals and graduate students. Events continued under the Folk Arts series and Welcome Back to Brooklyn Storytelling tent, but documentation was not consistent. The first full time Folklorist, Dr. Kay Turner, was hired in 2000. She approached the role as a way to work on "large frame ideas that looked at the importance of traditions within the context of things that were meaningful to Brooklyn."
Dr. Turner took an artist-first approach, often co-creating programs with artists and staging them at larger venues to attract a more general audience. Additional sponsorship allowed Folk Arts to produce multi week and annual programs, with expanded promotional reach. Highlights include Harborlore: Where the River Meets the Sea in Brooklyn's Folk Imagination, a series of 12 free dance, music and storytelling events exploring the role of water in Brooklyn's immigrant and diaspora communities; Folk Feet: Celebrating Traditional Dance in Brooklyn, a multi year project to identify, document and present the range of traditional dance practices in Brooklyn; and Brooklyn Maqam Arab Music Festival, a celebration of Arab music traditions in Brooklyn. Dr. Turner left Folk Arts in 2014 and was replaced by Christopher Mulé, who served as director until 2020, when BAC ended its affiliation with the Folk Arts program.
See series levels for a full history of each Folk Art program.
Oral histories (document genres); Interviews; Sound recordings; Videocassettes; Video recordings; Correspondence; Color prints (photographs); Slides (Photography); Audiocassettes; Exhibition records; Financial records; Dance; Songs (document genre); Music -- Performance; Independent films; Art -- Exhibitions; Concerts; Funeral rites and ceremonies -- New York (State) -- Kings County; Hurricane Sandy, 2012; Williamsburg Bridge (New York, N.Y.); September 11 Terrorist Attacks, 2001 -- Personal narratives; Storytelling; Folk art (traditional art); Folk dances
- Series 1: Early Programs
  Scope and Contents
  The items in this series document the events produced by the Folks Arts program from 1986-2000. Program Files include correspondence, contracts, brochures and fliers, publicity, and research materials. Also included are files kept by the various Folk Arts Directors while planning and executing their annual programs, including Kathleen Condon (1986-1989), Sean Galvin (1990-1991), Jessica Payne (1992), Justine McGovern (1993-1994), Ilana Abramovitch (1995), Richard Wolf (1996), Emily Botein (1997), and Nancy Groce (1998-99).
  Also included is a small group of resource files, arranged geographically and consisting of printed material and notes on arts and artists of the region. These files also contain material documenting funding efforts, including grant applications and reports. Audiovisual items in this series are recordings from programs produced by Folk Arts, compilations used for grant support, and several tapes of music by performers involved in Folk Arts programs. Cassettes also include interviews with performers and artists. Labeling on tapes is inconsistent. VHS tapes are program recordings and grant support. Boxes 102-106 appear at the end of the Audiovisual sub-series and include media submitted by artists, media used by Folk Arts directors for research, and media compiled from various programs. Labeling on these items is inconsistent.
  Binders contain photographs and slides taken during Folk Arts programs, dating 1988-2000, including images from the Storytelling Tent during the Welcome Back to Brooklyn events.
  Early Program Events:
  1987 Kathy Condon
  Adopt-a-landmark Folklife Series, Storytelling and other events relating to:
  Coney Island
  Lowe's Kings Theatre
  Brooklyn Waterfront
  Erasmus High School
  Coney Island Steeplechase
  African and Caribbean Collection at the Brooklyn Museum
  Gravesend Church and Cemetery
  New Utrecht Reformed Church and Cemetery
  West Indian- American Day Parade
  Folk Art and Artists Series
  Scandinavian Folk Arts:
  Walter Eriksson (accordionist)
  Doris Jensen (Norwegian rosemaler)
  Black Folk Arts:
  The Heavenly Tones (Gospel music)
  Virginia Hall and Molly Rives (quilters)
  Italian Folk Arts:
  Ridgewood/Bushwick Senior Center Music Group (folk and popular music)
  Vincenzo Ancona (wire sculpture)
  Puerto Rican Folk Arts:
  Ser Boricua es un honor/El Conjunto de Sunset Park (folk music)
  Pablo Falcon (toy maker)
  West Indian Folk Arts:
  Alvin Forteau and the Caribbean Dancers (Trinidadian dancing and drumming)
  Morris Stewart (Carnival costume maker)
  Storytelling Tent, Welcome Back to Brooklyn
  Topics include:
  Sunset Park
  South Brooklyn
  Immigration
  1989 Kathy Condon, Folk Art and Artists Series:
  Lebanese and Middle Eastern Arts:
  Simon Shaheen and Hanna Mirhige (Near Eastern traditional music)
  Basil Kazan (Byzantine liturgical chanter)
  Antoine Solounias (Byzantine iconographer)
  Lillian Habib (traditional Lebanese cooking)
  Jewish Arts:
  Klezmer Plus! (concert in memory of Dave Tarras)
  Rabbi Yehuda Clapman (Sofer, Hebrew religious scribe)
  Faigel Jacobson (religious embroidery and beadwork)
  Chinese Arts:
  Rebecca Shu-Min Fung, Chen Guo, Li Yu (dance)
  Zhang Bao Li (erhu, two-stringed fiddle)
  Woo Chai Meng (Ho Nan Shau Lin martial arts master, traditional healer and dragon maker)
  Puerto Rican Arts:
  El Conjunto de Sunset Park (traditional music)
  Jose Aviles (carver, santos de palo)
  Iraida Rivera (mundillo, bobbin lace artist)
  Maria Ponce (crochet artist and maker of capias)
  Afghan Arts:
  Sayed Farooq and Timor Karimi (traditional and popular music)
  Jamila and Mahmood Masumi and Nafas Gul Muradi (rug weaving and design)
  1990: Sean Galvin, Folk Art and Artists Series:
  Panamanian Arts and Artists:
  Pedro "Papi" Alonso (coppersmith)
  Gino Canalies and the Panamanian Folkloric Dance Company (dance)
  Silvia Fisher, Cornelia Cotillion Square Dance Club
  Gino Canalies and the Conjunto Folklorico de Panama (dance)
  Irish Arts and Artists
  Larry Otway (Currach builder)
  Tom Doherty (melodeon) and Maureen Doherty (accordion and flute)
  Donnie and Eileen Golden (stepdancers)
  Maureen Kennelly (Ceili dancer)
  Earle Mitchner (emcee for dance program)
  Caribbean East Indian Arts and Artists:
  Siew Paul Singh (Bhojpuri singer and harmonium player)
  Pandit Swasti Doobay (Hindu priest, sacred and symbolic rice and flower designs for puja, traditional invocation and worship of Hindu dieties)
  Sham Rampersad, Roopchan Rambharat and Jasmine Pancham (Caribbean folk and film songs)
  Sam Sugrim (tassa drumming ensemble)
  Lakshmi Mandir (Chowtal and Kirtan Group)
  Syrian Jewish Arts and Artists:
  Sandra Levy (Syrian foodways)
  Rae Dayan (Syrian foodways)
  Vita Isreal (oud player), with Hakki Obadia (violinist), George Bassile (kanoun) and Joseph Zaroura (darbokka)
  Cantor Elie Abadie (sacred and secular Pizmonim songs)
  Greek Arts and Artists:
  Father John Spilos (iconographer)
  Irene Mavris and Vasiliki Kourniotis (embroidery)
  George Stathos (clarino) and his Greek band, with George Jatzinocolaou (violin) and John Roussos (santouri)
  Athanasia Fidanidou and Dancers (dance)
  Department of Transportation/Triborough Bridge and Tunnel Authority
  Verrazano Narrows Bridge
  Sheepshead Bay
  Brooklyn Battery Tunnel
  Carroll Street Bridge
  1991 Sean Galvin, Folk Art and Artists Series:
  Andean Arts and Artists:
  Antara del Barrio, with Francisco Rodriguea, Leyder Dorado, Ricardo Silva, Cesar Ferreria (music)
  Ricardo Silva (panpipe maker)
  Ghanaian Arts and Artists:
  Selina A. Ahoklui (Adinkra textiles)
  Novisi Cultural Troop (dance)
  Polish Arts and Artists:
  Stefan Wrobel (accordion) and his ensemble
  Nadia Gryziec and Irene Polly (Pisanki demonstration)
  Cambodian Arts and Artists:
  Princess Nearyreth Dancers with Sk Melea, Ek Bonna and Ek Dary
  Heng Phem and the Mongkol Ensemble (drumming)
  Savath Chan (sculptor, mask decorator)
  Turkish Arts and Artists:
  The Turkish-American Youth Dancers, with Tayyar Akdeniz
  Mahmoud Efeturk, Sahara Restaurant ("Turkish Delight," traditional foodways)
  1992 Jessica Payne, Folk Arts Series:
  Hatian Arts and Artists:
  Frisner Augustin and La Troupe Makandal (music and dance)
  Lesly Calvin (Vodou flags and veve)
  Uri Domond (painter)
  Mexican Arts and Artists:
  Mariachi Tequilla with Yolanda Leticia (music)
  Miguel Angel Cossio (pinata maker)
  Dominican Arts and Artists:
  Pedro Checo y Aguja y su Conjunto Tipico Dominicano (merenge)
  Enevina Duran (flower maker)
  Indigenous Arts and Artists:
  The Young Blood Singers (Cherokee, Shinnecock, Montauk and Wampanouag music and dance)
  Donald Jackson (Cherokee porcupine quill work)
  Ina McNeil (Sioux beadwork)
  1993 Justine McGovern, Folk Arts '93:
  Black Arts and Artists:
  Wonder Boy and the Spiritual Voices (Brooklyn Gospel)
  Valarie Jean Bailey (quilting)
  Puerto Rican Arts and Artists:
  Bomba and Plena workshop with Los Pleneros de la 21 (music and dance)
  Jose Aviles (santos carver and jewelry maker)
  Jewish Arts and Artists:
  Shasmaqam (Bukharan-Jewish music and dance)
  Gennady Gutkin (Ukranian and Russian-Jewish music)
  Tibetan Arts and Artists:
  Nawabg Khechog (flute)
  Venerable Lobsang Samten (sand painting)
  Storytelling tent, Welcome Back to Brooklyn Arts Council
  Indigenous and Black storytelling traditions
  Brooklynites at work and Play I: making a community a home – Lefferts Manor
  Play: Brooklyn Summers, Steamy but Fun!
  Work: Brooklyn Women and Grass Roots Politics
  Brooklyn at Work and Play II: Growing up on "the Avenue" – Midde Eastern Atlantic Avenue
  1994 Justine McGovern, Folk Arts '94:
  Arabic Music and Foodways:
  Eddie Kochak and Hajji Obadia (music)
  Amina Ibrahim (foodways)
  Chinese Music and Calligraphy:
  Cornel Chan and his musicians
  Li Ng and her daughters Annie and Mary (calligraphy)
  Eastern European Music and Paper Crafts:
  Traditional music (produced in Cooperation with the Ethnic Folk Arts Center)
  Clara Lamers (paper cutting)
  Pakistani Music and Wedding Arts
  Mulazim Hussein, Quzi Shabbaz and choudry Ackbar (folk music)
  Nighat Faridi and her daughter Irrim Shai (mehndi rassam henna hand painting and other wedding-related women's arts)
  Storytelling Tent, Welcome Back to Booklyn
  Family Businesses: Working Out Together
  Public School Teachers: Brooklyn Schools, Brooklyn Stories
  West Indian Hair Braiders: The Business of Beauty, Brooklyn Style
  1995 Ilana Abramovitch, Folk Arts '95:
  Jewish Purim Music and Crafts:
  Ruben Benyamin (Persian Jewish singer)
  Leah Jirshfield Levin (traditional plaques welcoming the month of Adar)
  Mexican Storytelling and Dia de los Muertos Traditions:
  Elvira and Hortensia Colorado (storytelling)
  Albertano and Lilia Meza (Dia de los Muertos traditions)
  West Indian Carnival Music and Costume Making:
  Caribbean American Sports and Cultural Youth Movement (CASYM) Steel Orchestra of Brooklyn (steel pan music)
  Ray Morris (Carnival costume creator)
  Swedish Music and Crafts:
  Jeanne Eriksson Widman (accordion music)
  Gunhild Ljung (paper crafts)
  Tony Zupa and Joe Sclafani: working musicians who play Italian feasts, including the Giglio
  Linda MaQueen and her daughter: Madina Johnson: lives of women, being homeless
  Jerry Flynn: growing up in Brooklyn during Prohibition, sheep in Prospect Park, The Catholic school, etc.
  Ray Morris: West-Indian American Labor Day parade
  Grace Kelly: growing up in the 1910s
  Umma Group, including James Hardy: Neighborhood patrol group in Flatbush
  Kenny Koslowitz: subway system
  1996 Richard Wolf, Folk Arts Series 1996:
  Indo-Caribbean Music and Dance:
  U.S. #1 Tassa Drummers
  Singers and dancers from The Shri Ram Mandir (Hindu devotional music and singing)
  Singers and dancers from The Rajkumari Center (Indian classical dance)
  West African Music, Dance, Storytelling and Crafts:
  African Jaliya Kafo (Griot music, dance and storytelling)
  Dr. Selina Ahoklui (textile crafts)
  Garifuna Dance, Music, Crafts and Folklife:
  Ilagulei Garifuna Performing Arts Company (dance and music)
  Barbara Nunez (doll and dressmaking)
  Chinese Music, Acrobatics, Dance, Drama, Painting and Calligraphy:
  Tang Liang-xing and group (traditional instrumental music)
  Thomas Fu-Keung Lau (water color painting, poetry, calligraphy)
  Qi Shu Fang's Peking Opera Co. (dance, drama and acrobatics)
  Brooklyn Children's Museum Grand Reopening:
  Dancers from the Rajkumari Center (stories from Hindu mythology)
  The Shri Ram Mandir Kirtan Group (songs from the festival of spring and mandala designs in colored rice)
  African Jaliya Jafo (stories, songs and dances rom senegambia, Mail and Guinea)
  Brooklyn Children's Museum Breaking Ground; People and Plants:
  Ilagulei Garifuna Cultural Performing Arts Company
  Barbara Nunez (Garifuna clothing and doll making)
  Thomas Fu-Keung Lau (calligraphy and watercolor painting)
  Qi Shu Fang's Peking Opera Company
  Baseball:
  Harvey Frommer: New York City Baseball: The Last Golden Age
  Carl Price: Brooklyn Dodgers
  Sharon Robinson: Stealing Home
  Richard Rosenblum: Brooklyn Dodger Days
  Historic Brooklyn:
  John Gallagher: The Battle of Brooklyn, 1776
  Myrna Katz Frommer: It Happened in Brooklyn
  Philip Kasinitz: Caribbean New York: Black Immigration and the Politics of Race
  1997 Emily Botein, Folk Arts '97:
  Pakistani Music and Family Traditions:
  Shahid Kabir Ali (singer of qawwali, devotional music of Sufi Muslims)
  Anwari Rajput (cooking, sewing, henna wedding traditions)
  Yemeni Music, Dancing and Foods for Weddings:
  Shoshana Tubi (traditional singer)
  Faud Alkebsi (singer and oud player)
  Tziona Sharabi (foods for weddings)
  Italian Songs and Crafts for the Giglio Feast:
  Mark Pezzano (collects and sings giglio songs)
  Members of the Church of Our Lady of Mount Carmel (giglio builders)
  Africa in the Caribbean: Drumming and Drum Making:
  Junior Wedderburn (drum maker and player)
  Sekou Jawara (drum maker)
  Frisner Augustin (Vodou drumming)
  1998 Nancy Groce, BAC Folk Arts Series: Constructing Harmony: Traditional Music and Musical Instrument Making in Brooklyn
  Indigenous Music and Musical Instrument Making:
  The Manahata Indian Arts Council with Clifford Standing Deer and Ray Elk Silva (demonstrate the making and playing of Indigenous musical instruments)
  West Indian Steel Pan Making:
  Mickey Enoch, Master Steel Pan "Tuner" (steel pan builder)
  Despers U.S.A. Members (steel band performance)
  Middle Eastern Music and Musical Instrument Making:
  Jules Azzi (violin and oud maker)
  Najeeb Shaheen (oud player)
  Bassam Saba (ney/violin player)
  Russian Music and Musical Instrument Making:
  David Chrapkiewicz (Balalaika and violin maker)
  Tamara Volskaya (domra player)
  Anatoliy Trofimov (bayan/accordion player)
  Welcome Back to Brooklyn Festival: Brooklyn Arts Council Tradition Music Stage:
  The Kings County Ceili Band with Mat Mancuso (Irish)
  Tamara Volskaya and Anatoliy Trofimov with Russian Carnival (Russian)
  Desters, U. S. A. (West Indian)
  1999 Nancy Groce, BAC Folk Arts Series: Constructing Harmony:
  Afro-Cuban Drums, Drum-making and Drumming:
  Jay Bereck, Drum-maker and Ensemble
  Indo-Caribbean Drums, Drum-making and Drumming:
  Ramnarine Sasenairine and Ensemble
  West African Drums, Drum-making and Drumming from the Ivory Coast:
  Vado Diamande, Master Drummer and Ensemble
  Hatian Drums, Drum-making and Drumming:
  Frisner Augustin and Members of La Troupe Makandal
  Welcome Back to Brooklyn, BAC Stage:
  La Troupe Makandal (Afro-Hatian Music and Dance)
  Tony Demarco and Donny Goldon (Irish Traditional Music and Dance)
  Ray Cruz and Cruz Control (Latin Salsa)
  Despers USA (Trinidadian steel pan)
  Praise in the Park: Music of Faith Festival
  Red Hawk Indian Arts Council
  Choir of the Russian Orthodox Cathedral of the Transfiguration of Our Lord (liturgical music)
  Charlie Sonrey and his All Stars (African American Gospel)
  The Word (Spiritually-Inspired Big Band Jazz)
  Pizmonim (Middle Eastern music from the Jewish Sephardic Community Center)
  The Shri Ram Mandir (Indo-Caribbean Hindu music of praise)
  Please note that not every event includes a corresponding file or audiovisual item.
  Conditions Governing Access
  Due to sensitive personal information, materials in box 98, folder 10 are not open for research.
  - Sub-series 1.1: Program Files
    - Adopt-a-Landmark, 1986-1987 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Video Log, 1986-1987 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Publicity, 1977, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Release Form, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Student Documentation, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Contracts, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Log of Audio, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - Notes from Folklorists, 1987-1999 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - Correspondence, 1988 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - Publicity, 1988 (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - Release Forms, 1988 (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - Storytelling Tent, 1988 (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - Press Releases, 1988 (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - Budget, 1988 (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - Contracts, 1988 (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - Of, By and For Youth Museum, 1988 (Box 1, Folder 17)
    - Flyers and Brochures, 1988 (Box 1, Folder 18)
    - Correspondence, Internal, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 19)
    - Correspondence, Participants, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 20)
    - Correspondence, General, 1989 (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - Budget, 1989 (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - Contracts, 1989 (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - Flyers and Brochure, 1989 (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - Field Notes for Tapes, 1989 (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - Photographer, 1989 (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - Press Releases, 1989 (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - Publicity, 1989 (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - Storytelling Tent, 1989 (Box 2, Folder 9)
    - Releases, 1989 (Box 2, Folder 10)